was about to make the biggest mistake the entrepreneur
it may be well done that I changed my mind
it all started
when I exchanged 1 idea earlier today with my partner
I was also thinking yesterday about that the packaging
will come out as a really a continuation form
and not a break
learning is changing is recalculating the route every day bro
even for us no
warm up the noise understood bro let's play
let's play because otherwise it loses strength mano
we are together hug bye bye
my partner here where we are Tolentino
I was doing a big shit there,
man
doing wanting to make a new challenge I apologize
created bigger community
there's Charlie Brown and the crowd enjoying the brand
if i stop building now
everything can go to the bag is on
it's now that I need to build a relationship
with my points of sale
I came to give you 1 hello just brother this is fine my partner and then
you're fine
and then how are you and there darling
now we will give a continuity plan
everything hay you are benzão
bonzão fratello spoke good to see you
and then brother I just came to see how you are doing there
I'm not a sniper order is on
talk to people and find out how it's going
not everything is sale Brother
caraca finally
it took a while so I send you on zap
thanks bro thanks it's a satisfaction bro it's us
in that box there are fifty brownies
the golden bell is already here somewhere
who receive
can now win a t-shirt
congratulations is to everyone
our only 4
how come you don't call me bro
but general is enjoying speaking straight chat
ready bro now i did the replacement
of all points of sale
i have to do this to the fullest so that
my brand don't fall into oblivion it's on doidão
i apologize to you
won't do 1 parallel challenge
make turned to my doidão brand
until tomorrow